Here, we have an off the shoulder sleeve.
Which, I guess technically may not be an actual sleeve.
It might just be part of the shirt.
Because, I have my drawing as almost a rollover style.
Like, think Nine-O-Two-One-O bodysuits with the jean shorts that are cuffed.
And, they come off the shoulders.
They're spandex.
That's what I was trying to represent here.
But, the sleeve is whatever part of the fabric is or the garment is on the arms.
So, therefore part of your sleeve is attached in here to the bodice of the actual shirt.
Which, makes it not technically a sleeve.
But, just go with it.
And, we have it going off the shoulder.
And, then remember always when you're trying to show dimension and show that it is 3D to add that little back flip right there to show the back of the garment.
Because, if you're looking at an actual person you will be able to see parts of the backs of their clothes from the fronts, three dimensional.
And, then create the curve wherever you want it.
Lower or higher.
Whatever you want.